Ma…
Please, don't do that again.
Remember what I told you? I'll find a way.
I can't bear to see you suffer, my dear.
I'm not suffering.
I never said that I was suffering.
I promise you.
I'll get back at Billy.
[BILLY] They may be delusional.
They believe in their own version
of the truth.
But that still doesn't change the fact
Bea has to pay for what she did.
Wish me luck actually
falling asleep tonight.
[JORDAN] You want to fall asleep?
♪ My muse ♪
♪ Where's our destination? ♪
♪ You are the captain ♪
♪ I'll follow wherever you go ♪
- It's beautiful.
- ♪ Oh, baby ♪
♪ I'll ride your wave ♪
♪ Wherever it takes me ♪
♪ My heart won't be lost ♪
♪ Even if you let go, I'll come back ♪
[HUMMING]
♪ Stay right there, my love ♪
♪ I'm coming home ♪
[ABRUPT, UNSETTLING MUSIC]
[GASPS]
[BILLY] Hello, dude?
Could you come with me?
Miss, is there really no way we can look
at Mariela Mercado's files?
[HEAD NURSE]
I'm really sorry, ma'am, but you can't.
Those are confidential.
I'm sorry.
[BILLY] And fuel prices have
increased again! My gosh!
Even electricity!
Everything's getting pricier!
- That's why we have to go.
- [NURSE] Is that so?
[BILLY] We might get caught in the rain.
- I'm sorry for the trouble.
- [NURSE] It's fine.
[BILLY] Take care!
Do you know what caused the fire?
[CLERK] No one knows, miss.
All I heard was that Mariela survived.
And so did her youngest daughter.
But her eldest daughter died.
[JORDAN] When did the fire happen?
[CLERK] About 12 or 13 years ago, I think.
[BILLY] But the father
wasn't with them?
[CLERK]
No, he wasn't.
The rumor is that
Mariela's husband left her.
[JORDAN GRUNTS]
[JORDAN EXHALES SHARPLY]
It turns out Bea went through a lot.
But our question remains unanswered.
What's your connection to this?
She lied about her sister.
But what she said about her father?
That seems to be true.
Well, if her father is still alive,
maybe we can get answers from him.
Yes, of course. I will help you find him.
Someone caused trouble
at your house last night?
Yes. The mother of the woman
who's mad at Billy.
Why is she mad at Billy?
No idea.
Maybe because of envy.
I don't know why she hates Billy so much,
to the point that she even
conspired with a criminal.
A criminal?
[PRECIOUS] Yes.
Remember when I told you
someone broke into our house?
Apparently, he had a different motive.
He wanted to scare us. Especially Billy.
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SPRAY PAINT CAN HISSING]
- [BILLY GRUNTS]
- [BODY THUDS]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up.
[GRUNTS]
- Give up already!
- Help! Let me go!
[BILLY GRUNTING]
- Stop resisting!
- [GRUNTS]
Auntie Pres! Help!
Auntie, was that Billy?
My God, Billy!
Billy!
Billy?
Help! Please help us!
My God, Billy, what happened?
[PANICKED BREATHING]
Billy. Billy. Billy.
Help!
Please help us!
Billy? Billy. Billy. Billy.
My God!
Jordan!
- Jordan, help me!
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Auntie Pres!
- Billy?
- What happened to Billy?
- Watch her for a second.
I'll call an ambulance.
Dude.
What?!
Yes, that happened.
Well, authorities are now
hunting down that guy,
and the mother has been given a warning.
So, I hope things will be okay now.
Are things really okay?
I hope so.
Your son is in a fight.
- What?!
Where's Oliver?
He's over there.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[OLIVER] You think I won't fight you?
Let's see who's tough.
You might just end up crying.
You're such a mama's boy.
- Oh, I mean an auntie's boy.
- [BOY 1] Ooh!
She's not your mom, right?
What did you say, huh? Say that again.
- You can't do it.
- Say it. I dare you.
- Oliver!
- Come on!
- I can fight you, you know?
- Hey! Oliver!
Break it up!
Go back to your classroom.
What are you all looking at?
Go back to your classrooms.
Oliver, what happened?
He called me an auntie's boy.
It was embarrassing.
Why are you mad about that?
It's true that you're your
auntie's boy, isn't it?
Your Aunt Precious loves you so much.
There's nothing embarrassing about that.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You're right, Sir Eric.
I'm sorry.
Auntie, I love you.
- I'm sorry. I love you.
- Love you.
It's a good thing you were both here.
I'll go now.
- Thank you.
- Okay, go now.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I understand where my mom is coming from.
Of course she wanted to confront them.
But unfortunately,
it made the problem worse.
Why don't you just tell her the truth?
Are you out of your mind?
You want me to tell her the truth?
There are only two possible outcomes
if she finds out who Billy is.
Either she kills someone,
or she tries to kill herself again.
I don't want that to happen to Mama.
How long are you going to keep it hidden?
She's going to find out
the truth eventually.
If she finds out the truth,
Billy's done for.
I'll make her suffer
while I'm enjoying a good life.
That way, Mama won't have
to worry about anything.
But how can I do that?
I keep losing against her.
I don't even have money
to pay the electricity bill or our rent.
Plus, I'm being linked to your case.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Here.
What's this?
[BEA] This…?
Hey.
- What?
- Where did you get this?
From my part-time job.
- You stole this, didn't you?
- Of course not.
- I can't accept this.
- That's yours.
Take it.
I have nothing to lose anyway.
Except you.
All right then.
- [GRUNTS]
- [SOFT THUD]
That's so cheesy.
[CALOY CHUCKLES]
All right.
[MUSIC BECOMES STIRRING]
'Bi.
What?
There's something I need you to do.
[JORDAN] No trace.
It seems they erased everything.
Are they hiding from someone?
So, what does that mean?
They're a family of criminals?
Well, Caloy is a hacking expert.
He probably erased all info
about Bea's dad.
Don't worry.
I have to find something.
"Mercado."
Sorry for the hassle.
You got dragged into my problems again.
Your problems?
Dude, what are you even saying?
I'm doing this for you.
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- And LoveList.
If you go down, we all go down.
Am I going to let that happen?
Of course not.
Thank you.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JORDAN] Okay.
Ms. Talia? Ms. Talia!
- Yes?
- Ms. Talia, hi.
- Do you remember me?
- Uh…
- I'm sorry--
- I applied to your company.
- Bea. Bea Mercado.
- Oh. Oh, right!
Yes, um…
Ms. Talia, uh…
I hope you can hear me out.
You see, my mother is sick,
so I really need a job.
I know there's a high chance
that you won't hire me.
That's why I'm here.
I came to talk to you directly
to hopefully convince you.
- I know that the reason--
- [MOTORCYCLE ENGINE ROARING]
- Hey! Hey!
- [TALIA GASPS]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE ROARING]
[TALIA] Oh! Oh my God!
[GASPS] Are you okay?
Oh my goodness!
- Oh…
- [BEA GRUNTS]
You're wounded!
[SOFT GROAN] I'm okay, ma'am.
- Are you okay?
- Yes. Here's your bag.
Bea, right?
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you so much.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Look at this kid.
[JUDE, YOUNG JORDAN CHUCKLING]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Jade?
Jade!
Mommy!
[VOICE SHAKING] Mommy!
[SOBS] Mommy!
[PAPERS RUSTLING]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[HEELS CLACKING]
- [BEA] Oh! Hi!
- [HR OFFICER] Hi.
You didn't call me.
Never mind, that's okay.
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
Hello, Ma?
Perhaps I should find a job.
I'm your mother. Of the two of us,
I should be the one working.
Why do you want to work all of a sudden?
It's fine, Ma.
When Papa left us, you and Abi
worked yourselves to the bone
for our family.
Now, it's my turn.
Did you find a decent company this time?
Yes, Ma.
They made me a supervisor.
They did?! That's my daughter!
That Billy can't look down on you now!
[CHUCKLES]
Anyway, I have to go, Ma.
We're quite busy here.
Bye.
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CALOY] Sorry.
I was too rough, so you got dragged.
It's fine. It made our act
even more convincing.
Ms. Talia really felt bad for me.
- But I hurt you.
- Tsk!
I said it's okay.
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Bea.
- Oh! Ma'am!
Uh, Ms. Talia, I haven't gotten
the chance to thank you.
Thank you so much, ma'am, for hiring me
despite the fact that
I have a police record.
I'm so grateful.
You know, I believe in second chances.
And I also believe
that you deserve a second chance.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Because of that, I'll do my best.
That said, I should get back to work.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
- Okay.
- Excuse me, ma'am.
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[NO AUDIBLE DIALOG]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
I promise, from here on,
it only gets better,
because every Filipina
deserves to feel safe
and empowered in love.
Thank you.
Thank you!
- [APPLAUSE]
- [GUSHING]
How was it? Be honest.
- No notes, chief.
- [BILLY] Hmm?
Yes, you delivered it so well!
- Right?
- You're awesome!
- [CHARM] Perfect!
- I didn't talk too fast?
- [TONI] No, you're good!
- [CHARM] You did so well!
- [MARJ] I think it's perfect.
- Guys?
So, I have good news.
I have a potential sponsor,
and it's…
Talia & Co., the jewelry brand!
[GIGGLES]
- Wow!
- Yeah!
Do you guys know how huge this is?
I went to their showroom once,
and their engagement rings are beautiful!
Oh?
You're checking out rings?
Shouldn't that be Ralph's job?
Perhaps she was inspired by Val.
Maybe she wants to be the one to propose.
- [AWKWARD LAUGHTER]
- Sorry, what's the tea?
Anyway!
Do you want this sponsorship deal or not?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
What do you think?
[TONI] It sounds great.
I mean, that's a good partnership.
- Okay.
- Okay!
- Let's do it!
- [CLAPS]
Thank you, Val.
Good.
Because this sponsorship
is already in the bag.
They just have one request, though.
Okay…
They want you to wear this
to the awards night.
This necklace costs 30 million.
Oh.
[TONI] Gosh.
[BILLY] Wow.
[CHARM] It's beautiful!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Our collaboration
with celebrity influencer Maxie
was a success.
Aside from the exposure,
we experienced
increased traffic on our website
after it was released.
Thank you very much, Hannah,
for that presentation.
Ever since we rolled out this campaign,
there has been an increase in
the number of our followers.
And of course, this translates into
sales!
So we are continuing this campaign
with our next partner,
Billy Cariño of LoveList.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TALIA] She is the perfect
next partner for us.
More than just having a big following
and being a businesswoman,
she is relevant.
And the profile of LoveList members,
it has the demographics
of our target market.
Imagine!
If she is wearing one of our power pieces,
what a statement it will make.
What do you think?
It's a great idea, right?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Like I've said before,
just use me.
Anything, everything you tell me to do,
I'll do it all.
I'll help you.
- What do you think?
- Sounds great!
Yes!
Uh, Bea?
- Ma'am?
- [TALIA] Yes?
Yes, I agree with you, Ms. Talia!
Very good.
I think she'll make a wonderful partner
for our event.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
We hit the jackpot with this!
This will be a huge blow to Billy!
Just tell me when and where.
How does it look?
[CHARM] Wow, it's so pretty!
Definitely worth 30 million!
Keep your eyes on it later, okay?
We can't afford to lose it.
- [HUMMING]
- [GUITAR STRUMMING]
[JORDAN] Sorry.
When you sing,
you give us all the feels.
But why do you seem
so distracted today?
Just imagine you're singing
to the love of your life.
[JORDAN] I searched
every corner of the Net.
[BILLY] Mm-hmm?
But I couldn't find anything
about Bea's dad
or her family.